[{"version": "1", "index": 0, "hash": "9df1c16e82351bd6abc74d230391cd1e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ser", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to be (essential/permanent quality)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 1, "hash": "509d2216087fed59c56365ac2f8271ef", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "haber", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to have (to do something, auxiliary verb)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 2, "hash": "04f4f77f0bb047ac524e0ba532f122cf", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "estar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to be (health, location, state)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 3, "hash": "26f5581c11020176f12bf8cd3ea2fa24", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tener", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to have"}, {"version": "1", "index": 4, "hash": "98ddd921f5a0efaf582fd4c7f402401c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "hacer", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to do, make"}, {"version": "1", "index": 5, "hash": "6a065a3b0f83da435a7e1f5b7c7c107e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "poder", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to be able, can"}, {"version": "1", "index": 6, "hash": "552b49f02401a4b933948373a62bc79d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "decir", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to say, tell"}, {"version": "1", "index": 7, "hash": "d74eea4899a61f9fcbc527ef988ea0ff", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ir", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to go"}, {"version": "1", "index": 8, "hash": "0812f14f43315611dd0ef462515c9d00", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ver", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to see"}, {"version": "1", "index": 9, "hash": "ac638a13498ffe51c65a6ae0bf7089fd", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "dar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to give"}, {"version": "1", "index": 10, "hash": "2bde79bff687ae45f1354cde4324ccdd", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "saber", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to know (information)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 11, "hash": "c2a9a78d6b4268949ee341e4576afbfb", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "querer", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to want, love"}, {"version": "1", "index": 12, "hash": "bb52e40c0ebe2ac14c85bbb1e1dd086c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "llegar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to arrive, come, reach"}, {"version": "1", "index": 13, "hash": "c13a9518c16847bcf599888ab85099bf", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pasar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to pass, to spend (time), to happen"}, {"version": "1", "index": 14, "hash": "3d56eb4a68de80aeba42404e1a5544c4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "deber", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to owe, must, should, ought to"}, {"version": "1", "index": 15, "hash": "cff5a90f076c736c1d9a9fa644a7bb9c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "poner", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to put, place, set"}, {"version": "1", "index": 16, "hash": "d84e71d2af7aaf01484063b73052d5b0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "parecer", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to seem, appear"}, {"version": "1", "index": 17, "hash": "9bd506c67d5369b767d9db26e89ff5bc", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "quedar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to stay, remain"}, {"version": "1", "index": 18, "hash": "bf7eceea6674d4751715b628f9ee409d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "creer", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to believe"}, {"version": "1", "index": 19, "hash": "6bf62abc853d62b2cbb4b98aa987613b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "hablar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to speak"}, {"version": "1", "index": 20, "hash": "c60398f30370bb2a2c060e284f0d9fa4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "llevar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to carry, bring"}, {"version": "1", "index": 21, "hash": "ffb9faa62bc4ed79ed3d9b127cdf3f80", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "dejar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to leave, abandon, to let, allow"}, {"version": "1", "index": 22, "hash": "4fd76e8e679bbde8563ff888c12e4d92", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "seguir", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to follow, continue"}, {"version": "1", "index": 23, "hash": "8f5e15b75bab31c9e8de376ab30ab090", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "encontrar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to find, encounter"}, {"version": "1", "index": 24, "hash": "86d49e6406aa824b20c1888a3b83cafd", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "llamar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to call, to name"}, {"version": "1", "index": 25, "hash": "2108a729ea8429b7d65d35543016d664", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "venir", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to come"}, {"version": "1", "index": 26, "hash": "a68edf25b239cc48c98dbbcb824c72f6", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pensar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to think"}, {"version": "1", "index": 27, "hash": "4f004a55c2cfd7a24efe33bae5711b11", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "salir", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to leave, go out"}, {"version": "1", "index": 28, "hash": "1355df74a25c2afa02592030bdedc24b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "volver", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to return, go back"}, {"version": "1", "index": 29, "hash": "4e3fce60553f2b5b44fd829ab793f701", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tomar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to take, drink"}, {"version": "1", "index": 30, "hash": "890ce58e5f508db41ca4a83146fcf51b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "conocer", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to know (people, places)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 31, "hash": "1d7aaf100fcfab1adcf9bfaa66bd0173", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "vivir", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to live"}, {"version": "1", "index": 32, "hash": "350aef0dfc8134a2fc163861d1996a7e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sentir", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to feel, regret"}, {"version": "1", "index": 33, "hash": "c7d03804bd49109712571c97b1bbe340", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tratar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to treat, handle"}, {"version": "1", "index": 34, "hash": "cacf58f4ce8a01783e6fb4479e0e5482", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "mirar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to watch, look at"}, {"version": "1", "index": 35, "hash": "1bbb40f658706dae1a3ac7773dad4473", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "contar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to count, relate, tell"}, {"version": "1", "index": 36, "hash": "cd4b6e600acedfe908fe3e556c456bd8", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "empezar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to begin, start"}, {"version": "1", "index": 37, "hash": "cb72558ab3582f4b10c70910f60e7416", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "esperar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to wait for, to hope"}, {"version": "1", "index": 38, "hash": "5035d74e69d3d3e0ea1d07c0df7687c0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "buscar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to search for, look for"}, {"version": "1", "index": 39, "hash": "99907b3e15ca745b6544f29d726fc2d3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "existir", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to exist"}, {"version": "1", "index": 40, "hash": "b2eccf65385e0138e26ae97e89e88a0c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "entrar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to enter, go in, come in"}, {"version": "1", "index": 41, "hash": "1d76aa32e183f897ce5f6b96a81bf372", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "trabajar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to work"}, {"version": "1", "index": 42, "hash": "bd4c12baec0adbfab4333d81a05abc2f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "escribir", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to write"}, {"version": "1", "index": 43, "hash": "03f95d14d7acee7d81754dbcf34ae3dd", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "perder", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to lose"}, {"version": "1", "index": 44, "hash": "cd818ae33069f21d413e461a5c6778a8", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "producir", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to produce"}, {"version": "1", "index": 45, "hash": "02440959293edaac83f99e92ce971809", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ocurrir", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to occur, happen"}, {"version": "1", "index": 46, "hash": "eb4592e0caf19f6b2d5357e004888818", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "entender", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to understand"}, {"version": "1", "index": 47, "hash": "cba4a3b940252254ddd778cac446b262", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pedir", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to request, ask for"}, {"version": "1", "index": 48, "hash": "985603f48c3382a982c860384715135d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "recibir", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to receive, to welcome, greet"}, {"version": "1", "index": 49, "hash": "867a5a115b218a5bfdc709fa3afb71fd", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "recordar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to remember, remind"}, {"version": "1", "index": 50, "hash": "a95e998bf96ba3bc24e31c546c69c80d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "terminar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to finish, end"}, {"version": "1", "index": 51, "hash": "40f3d08a8addd234ec4cd24a6bb893b9", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "permitir", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to permit, allow"}, {"version": "1", "index": 52, "hash": "2ad0ebc2b45e26dd6eb8eb0aa3424f66", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "aparecer", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to appear, show up"}, {"version": "1", "index": 53, "hash": "3b75fcc1ceb2dbda88417e9df8aabf2b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "conseguir", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to get, obtain"}, {"version": "1", "index": 54, "hash": "eef799b0a3dc534cbc84f8ab05bb7b41", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "comenzar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to begin, start, commence"}, {"version": "1", "index": 55, "hash": "629fe602c9df1aa2cc6a8d7db597191b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "servir", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to serve"}, {"version": "1", "index": 56, "hash": "1acf3b8feac4a0434974360a62159200", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sacar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to take out, stick out"}, {"version": "1", "index": 57, "hash": "b7dbfd624c6f3fc1ad485f4c761f9cb8", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "necesitar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to need, require"}, {"version": "1", "index": 58, "hash": "ee3cf03c338551cd036b63dca83b04b9", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "mantener", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to maintain, get"}, {"version": "1", "index": 59, "hash": "73c900936b08349bb725509f68b43562", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "resultar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to turn out (to be)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 60, "hash": "3f60eb7939d4fdcb9244c0999b175f09", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "leer", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to read"}, {"version": "1", "index": 61, "hash": "2047c8c7ff6261a50a8e9a0ef73f2ae1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "caer", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to fall"}, {"version": "1", "index": 62, "hash": "a9c5c54a0bed5ecd0340dbc718225efc", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cambiar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to change"}, {"version": "1", "index": 63, "hash": "9ef0698c58ac5790d53b2e5d832c060e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "presentar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to introduce"}, {"version": "1", "index": 64, "hash": "1d11aefafdea5ee7bbac909cd5f97dd3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "crear", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to create, to make"}, {"version": "1", "index": 65, "hash": "bdc03f4cd2d6c51d61457d843c5be59a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "abrir", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to open"}, {"version": "1", "index": 66, "hash": "00017ba23991316bf98c6f62d42ec477", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "considerar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to consider"}, {"version": "1", "index": 67, "hash": "9a991c4c991aead970906e76e65580f6", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "o\u00edr", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to hear"}, {"version": "1", "index": 68, "hash": "1b20d201f99a4c83823ae6511cad884c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "acabar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to finish, end"}, {"version": "1", "index": 69, "hash": "3a59a2cc3af5820fec7de2a66d45ccf9", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "convertir", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to convert, change"}, {"version": "1", "index": 70, "hash": "e5e2227d92d41bae8da556d431978c66", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ganar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to win, gain, earn, get, acquire"}, {"version": "1", "index": 71, "hash": "d04f6b42d09ec69c1c0fef8c3b4f3ea4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "formar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to form, shape, fashion, make"}, {"version": "1", "index": 72, "hash": "6b131918402bca9a0a830ec676b2fc94", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "traer", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to bring, to get, fetch, to carry"}, {"version": "1", "index": 73, "hash": "cf5f1c5c3091f9e3fe3f3cf2e36a0274", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "partir", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to divide, to leave"}, {"version": "1", "index": 74, "hash": "3b6bebab18911f2f524c047b989aa08d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "morir", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to die"}, {"version": "1", "index": 75, "hash": "c1345b53ba505dbfd198058e47a37ece", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "aceptar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to accept, approve, to agree to"}, {"version": "1", "index": 76, "hash": "b0cf78741653b522b0e62a35675ee470", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "realizar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to achieve, attain, accomplish"}, {"version": "1", "index": 77, "hash": "f26d39eb4f92741f6be80aebe1c1973d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "suponer", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to suppose"}, {"version": "1", "index": 78, "hash": "a2cf809bd733fa16e7fbb48598672906", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "comprender", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to understand, comprehend"}, {"version": "1", "index": 79, "hash": "52c36de83d6046645fd51f8ada263859", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "lograr", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to get, obtain, to achieve, attain"}, {"version": "1", "index": 80, "hash": "775d86a5ca2d13ed34b025d506f743c1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "explicar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to explain"}, {"version": "1", "index": 81, "hash": "f037bf0143f587fddebc939fff013b2e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "preguntar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to ask, inquire"}, {"version": "1", "index": 82, "hash": "a88fcdf2a458912005b4982f5d1a877e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tocar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to touch, to play (an instrument)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 83, "hash": "754c6c4629faeceb2cbc434b3b1d9311", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "reconocer", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to recognize"}, {"version": "1", "index": 84, "hash": "f1ce9295c437f807d4b41f08a6d95c7f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "estudiar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to study"}, {"version": "1", "index": 85, "hash": "28a1090439095eba4e550b6b2593b359", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "alcanzar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to reach, catch up"}, {"version": "1", "index": 86, "hash": "3abab8f2f9e26c105be415814e549101", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "nacer", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to be born"}, {"version": "1", "index": 87, "hash": "188d8ee70a616892dbdfbd02f13e2e6f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "dirigir", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to direct"}, {"version": "1", "index": 88, "hash": "f99046b2c43def36b873b23800f7158b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "correr", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to run"}, {"version": "1", "index": 89, "hash": "1cf0b361bdfa933ca3f54c7ab110daa9", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "utilizar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to use, utilize"}, {"version": "1", "index": 90, "hash": "ad095d51d7f48ca396f4e5315e08b1ff", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pagar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to pay, pay for"}, {"version": "1", "index": 91, "hash": "358ade38f4d20bc7927d4a4d5c331c27", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ayudar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to help"}, {"version": "1", "index": 92, "hash": "eeaf293f296237236945dfe0ee5e7694", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "gustar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to please, be pleasing"}, {"version": "1", "index": 93, "hash": "b0dd367c4b1fe64fc5f91e4396f6fd36", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "jugar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to play (a game or sport)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 94, "hash": "e9f14aa1c1ba411ea40af378a207f32b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "escuchar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to listen, hear"}, {"version": "1", "index": 95, "hash": "6b22e9237f7d16b3d28f0c0f5e31f194", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cumplir", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to fulfil, carry out"}, {"version": "1", "index": 96, "hash": "275a5e94fda32bba3e5a59fbd3b71cff", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ofrecer", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to offer"}, {"version": "1", "index": 97, "hash": "c7ebbeeb19ab1fb32e9142963c1b7592", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "descubrir", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to discover"}, {"version": "1", "index": 98, "hash": "9e2032eaba743a43f870d9f7fbcf0262", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "levantar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to raise, to lift"}, {"version": "1", "index": 99, "hash": "75f857c4b3497f4bbc63d11fff0473ec", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "intentar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "to try, attempt"}]